PROFESSOR: So what has to
go in the search space?
Well, we still need everything we
needed for eating the dots--
Pac-Man's current position and some
representation of what dots are left,
so, say, a Boolean list for each dot,
whether it's still present.
Now suddenly we care about the power
pellets, too, so we need a list of
which power pellets are present so we
know whether or not we've already
eaten them.
And the important thing that we add in
this problem is this notion of the
ghosts have to stay scared.
That means in the successor function we
need to know whether or not we're
still safe.
We need to know whether or not there's
time left on the scared timer, and so
the search state has to encode all of
the agent position, the dot Boolean
bit vector, the power pellet Boolean bit
vector, and the remaining scared
time on the ghost timers.